isac.gov.in 2019-05-27

# Privacy Policy

Home : Privacy Policy  Last updated on: 01-Apr-2015

Thanks for visiting website of U R Rao Satellite Centre , Bengaluru and reviewing our privacy policy.

We collect no personal information, like names or addresses, when you visit our website. If you choose to provide that information to us â€“ like filling out a feed back form, with an e-mail address or postal address, and submitting it to us through the website, we use that information to respond to your message, and to help you get the information you have requested. 

Our website never collects information or creates individual profiles for commercial marketing. While you must provide e-mail address for localized response to any incoming questions or comments to us, we recommend that you do NOT include any other personal information. 

We do collect some technical information when you visit to make your visit seamless. This website records your visit and logs few information for statistical purposes - your serverâ€™s address; the type of browser you use; the date and time you access the site; the pages you have accessed and the documents downloaded. We will not identify users or their browsing activities, except when a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect the service providerâ€™s logs. 

Site Security Policy 

  * For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this government computer system employs commercial software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorised attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.
  * Except for authorised law enforcement investigations, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. Raw data logs are used for no other purposes and are scheduled for regular deletion.
  * Unauthorised attempts to upload information or change information on this service are strictly prohibited and are punishable under the Indian IT Act.
